(Leonard:)They're probably
just all staring at the sky.
(Sheldon:)All right, what we need now
is a tactical retreat.
Did you see Stargate
where they found themselves on a planet...
(Sheldon:)...with a culture based loosely
on Earth's Athens and Sparta?
(Sheldon:)Not important.
Leonard, Raj and I are gonna burst out
the door and run away.
(Sheldon:)Howard will cover us.
But why don't I run away
and you cover me?
(Sheldon:)Because you chose your mother's veins
over victory.
(Sheldon:)On three. One, two, three, go!
[ALL SCREAMING
AND PAINTBALLS FIRING]
(Howard:)I had to take her.
It's almost bathing-suit weather.
[PAINTBALLS FIRING]
[HOWARD SHRIEKS]
I surrender, don't shoot.
They went that way.
LESLIE:
Howard, I'm on your team.
(Howard:)Oh, Leslie, thank God.
- Where's the rest of your squad?
- Uh...
(Howard:)They left me here to die.
(Howard:)What about yours?
- Dead. All of them.
- Sorry.
(Leslie:)Don't be.
(Leslie:)It was friendly fire.